cpcc.edu 2007-12-11

# Central Piedmont Community College: Online Privacy Policy

**Online Privacy Policy**

* * *

This document describes Central Piedmont Community College's (hereafter referred to as CPCC) policy regarding information received about you during visits to our web site. The amount and type of information received depends on how you use the site. 

Limitation on Scope of Content:

The CPCC web site contains information regarding CPCC and its education and training services. All pricing information referred to in this site is in U.S. dollars. 

No Representation or Warranty:

CPCC reserves the right to modify the information contained in this site at any time without notice. While CPCC makes all reasonable efforts to insure that all material on this site is correct, accuracy cannot be guaranteed and CPCC does not assume any responsibility for the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of any information contained in this site.   
This site and all information and materials contained herein, is provided to you "as is" without warranty of any kind. This site may contain hypertext links to other World Wide Web sites which are completely independent of this site. CPCC makes no representation or warranty as to the accuracy, completeness or authenticity of the information contained in any such hypertext link, and any hypertext link to another person or entity shall not in any manner be construed as endorsement by CPCC of such person's or entity's World Wide Web site, products or services. Your linking to any other off-site pages or other sites is at your own risk.   
Your confidential use of this site cannot be guaranteed by CPCC. CPCC shall not be responsible for any harm that you or any person may suffer as a result of a breach of confidentiality in respect to your use of this site or any information you transmitted to this site. 

Normal Web Site Usage:

You can visit CPCC's web site to access education/training service information or use our online tools (online courses, etc.) without telling us who you are and without revealing any personal information. The only information we collect and store during normal web site usage is the web site that referred you to us, the pages you request and the date and time of those requests.   
We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to improve the usefulness of customer visits. During normal web site usage, we do not collect or store personally identifiable information such as name, mailing address, email address, phone number or social security. 

Collection of Personally Identifiable Information:

There are instances where CPCC requests personally identifiable information to provide the web site visitor a service or correspondence (mailed class schedules and brochures). This information, such as name, mailing address, email address, type of request and possibly additional information, is collected and stored in a manner appropriate to the nature of the data by CPCC and is used to fulfill your request. CPCC makes every effort to insure the secure collection and transmission of sensitive user information using industry accepted data collection and encryption methodologies such as SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) and PGP (Pretty Good Privacy). The information you provide is used by CPCC to improve the services we provide you. It is never provided to any other company for that company's independent use. 

Use of Cookies:

Cookies are pieces of information that a web site transfers to an individual's hard drive for record-keeping purposes so that we may track site and user activity. The use of cookies is an industry standard and you will find them at most major web sites. By showing how and when visitors use the site, cookies help CPCC to better track which those areas of our site which are popular and those which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on such data as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, it is possible that some parts of the site will not function properly if you do so.

Copyright/Trademark Ownership:

The information in this site is protected by copyright. You may only use the information, text or graphics contained in this site for your personal use and may not reproduce, adapt, or publish it, in whole or in part, for any purpose without the express written consent of CPCC. The CPCC logo may not be used, downloaded, copied or distributed in any way. 

By using this site, you signify your assent to the CPCC Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use this site. We reserve the right to change CPCC's Online Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice or consent.
